<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Search><pages Count="16"><page Index="1"><![CDATA[People















                     On Earth




















        Book Created and illustrated

                      Sarra Ben Amara]]></page><page Index="2"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="3"><![CDATA[About 200,000 years ago, early people only lived in


       Africa. Today, almost seven billion people live all over



       Earth! People have changed our planet in many ways.]]></page><page Index="4"><![CDATA[What Have People Changed?


   Some places on Earth haven't changed very much. They are


   natural areas, like rainforests and national parks. Natural


   areas are important because they are homes for many plants


   and animals. We need to care for these areas so that plants


   and animals can live there in the future.]]></page><page Index="5"><![CDATA[In other areas, people have changed many things. In rural


   areas, farmers have cut down trees and they have cleared land


   to grow crops for people to eat. In urban areas, like towns


   and cities, people have built lots of homes and other buildings.

   They have also built roads, bridges, and tunnels.]]></page><page Index="6"><![CDATA[What Have People Changed?


   Earth gives us lots of resources like food and other


   products from plants and animals. It also gives us water to


   drink and air to breathe.]]></page><page Index="7"><![CDATA[These natural resources are renewable - they replace


     themselves naturally. We can get more of these resources,


     but we need to share them with other people.]]></page><page Index="8"><![CDATA[In some parts of the world, people don't have enough food


    or enough clean water. Earth also gives us mineral resources,

    like metals, that we use to make products in factories.]]></page><page Index="9"><![CDATA[We burn fossil fuels, like oil, coal, and gas, to produce


    energy. These resources are non-renewable. We can't get any

    more, so we need to use them carefully.]]></page><page Index="10"><![CDATA[Waste and Pollution


    We throwaway too much waste, and this is bad for our


    planet. We need to reduce the amount of waste that we


    produce - we can recycle more things, like paper, plastic,


    glass, and metal.]]></page><page Index="11"><![CDATA[Our cars and factories produce smoke that pollutes the air.


    In some cities, it can be difficult to breathe because there's

    so much pollution in the air. Some factories pollute our


    water and soil. We should build more modern factories that


    don't produce so much pollution.]]></page><page Index="12"><![CDATA[Global Warming


    Scientists think that a new greenhouse period is starting.


    Earth is getting warmer, and many glaciers are melting, like


    the ones on Mount Kilimanjaro in Tanzania. Why is this


    happening? For the last 150 years, people have burned lots

    of fossil fuels, and this makes gases like carbon dioxide.]]></page><page Index="13"><![CDATA[The carbon dioxide is increasing the natural greenhouse


    effect, and making Earth warmer. This is called global


    warming. We need to produce less carbon dioxide. We also

    need to protect our forests and plant new trees. Trees use


    carbon dioxide and slow down global warming.]]></page><page Index="14"><![CDATA[Caring for Our Planet

    We live on a beautiful planet that has been here for billions


    of years. Earth gives us everything that we need to live.


    Now we need to care for our planel so that our children


    and our grandchildren can enjoy It in the future, too!]]></page><page Index="15"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="16"><![CDATA[Quiz Time]]></page></pages></Search>